反恐24小时
第九季 第7集
前情提要
但若海勒總統不向我認罪
But unless President Heller surrenders himself to me
上千的倫敦市民
thousand of people in London
將替他而死
will die in his stead.
玛戈
阿尔哈拉兹
納維德，我是姐姐
Naveed, it's your sister.
我很擔心你
I'm worried about you.
我們是否還需離開倫敦？
Are we still getting out of London?
1个未接来电
1条新语音消息
-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
你知道這事？
Did you know about this?
不知道
No.
西蒙娜
阿尔哈拉兹
若是納維德打算
If Naveed had planned
翻译 筱宸葭
帶他姐姐離開倫敦
to take his sister out of London
那他一定暴露了我們的計劃
he must've told her about our operation.
翻译 lady5bird
去找她
Go to her.
我相信你能做好分內的事
I trust you to do what needs to be done.
翻译 不再的华年
帶上你女兒
Grab your daughter
馬上離開倫敦
and leave London right now.
翻译 pizzamx
等等，你幹什麼？
Wait, what are you doing?
報警
Calling the police.
校对 诸星龟龟
不要，不要，求你了
No. No. Please.
雅斯敏，快跑！
Yasmin, get out!
對不起
I'm so sorry.
特效 筱宸葭
救命啊！
Somebody help!
统筹 筱宸葭
雅斯敏，等等！
Yasmin, wait!
布德羅主任
Mr. Boudreau
我正在審視
I'm reviewing the
總統簽署關於傑克·鮑爾的轉移令
transfer order that the president signed for Jack Bauer.
詹姆斯·海勒
美利坚合众国总统
办公厅主任
马克·布德罗
難道您對此事
Is there some reason
會牽涉到海勒總統有什麼難言之隱？
you are uncomfortable involving President Heller?
我們私下見面聊吧
Let's meet privately.
我的丈夫出賣國家機密
I was married to a man who was convicted of
給別國政府
selling state secrets to a foreign government.
特工
凯特·摩根
我發現我們的檔案裏有古怪
I found something weird in our archives
跟凱特的丈夫有關的文件
case files related to Kate's husband.
我需要運行涅槃恢復程序的授權
I need authorization to run a phoenix retrieval.
現在這件事你還是緩緩吧
You better hold off on that for now.
我的一個分析員一直在調查
One of my analysts has been digging around
亞當·摩根的數據文件
Adam Morgan's data files.
CIA分局局长
史蒂夫·纳瓦罗
如果你陷害她丈夫的證據被公諸於世
If the evidence you planted against her husband gets out
我們可保護不了你
there won't be any way for us to protect you.
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲控制了
Margot Al-Harazi has six U.S. drones
六架美國無人機
under her control.
你認識的那個軍火商
This arms dealer that you know
你確信他能讓我們找到她的藏身之處？
are you sure he can lead us to her whereabouts?
我相信他能
I believe he can.
他和瑪戈有多年生意往來，瑪戈信任他
He's done business with her for years, she trusts him.
傑克·鮑爾打算接頭一個
Jack Bauer intends to draw out
阿爾哈拉茲的生意夥伴
a business associate of Al-Harazi's.
首相先生，海勒在秘密接受
Sir, Heller's being secretly treated
老年癡呆癥的治療
for Alzheimer's.
聯繫軍情五處，派一個小隊過去
Get hold of MI5. Assemble a team.
這事兒我們自己處理
We'll handle this ourselves.
設置一個安全路徑
Set up a secure link.
傑克，你若能讓拉斯克
Jack, if you can get Rask
登陸此賬戶
to log into the account
我們也就能追蹤他與瑪戈的
we should be able to trace any of his interactions
一切往來信息
with Margot from there.
所有人都不許動！軍情五處！
Nobody move, MI5!
我搞定了，傑克
I've got it, Jack.
找到關於瑪戈的信息了嗎？
Did you manage to get anything on Margot?
就一個手機號碼
Just a phone number, a mobile
不過手機目前在倫敦南部某處
but the phone's somewhere in South London.
以下事件发生在
下午17:00 至下午18:00 之间
基弗
萨瑟兰
伊冯娜·斯特拉霍夫
泰特·多诺万
玛丽·莱恩·莱杰斯库
威廉·德韦恩
她突然衝到前面來
She just ran out in front of me.
格本加·阿金纳格贝
她好像在追人
Uh... it was like, she was chasing someone.
一個小女孩
Uh... a little girl.
什麼女孩？
What girl?
那兒，就是她
There, her.
贾尔斯·马特蒂
謝謝
Thank you.
迈克尔·温科特
你好啊
Hey, there.
本杰明·布拉特
你認識那個女人嗎？
Do you know that woman?
她是你媽媽？
Is she your mum?
她殺了我媽媽
She killed my mum.
基姆·瑞弗
客 串
米歇尔·费尔利
埃米莉·伯林顿
利亚姆·加里根
罗斯·麦克科尔
亚当·辛克莱
斯坦利·汤森
埃米尔·布特罗斯
谢莉·康恩
亚历克斯·拉尼佩坤
斯蒂芬·弗雷
你幹什麼？！
Hey. What'd you think you're doing?!
他和我一起的
He's with me.
我已經很給你面子了
I've given you some leeway
因為你救了我的人
because of what you did for my men.
不過別忘了規矩
But there are still protocols.
剪 辑
凯西·罗尔斯
我才不管你什麼規矩
I don't give a damn about your protocols.
軍情五處不該來的
MI5 shouldn't have been here.
你們干涉了我的行動
You interfered with my operation
差點害死我們
almost got us killed.
我是奉命行事
I had my orders.
誰下的令？
From who?
首相辦公室
The Prime Minister's office.
你們總統可以和他交涉
Your president can take it up with him.
他一定會的
I'm sure he will.
我会打给你
你能堅持嗎？
How're you holding up?
艺 术 指 导
乔纳森·李
我沒事
I'm okay.
只要是值得的
Just tell me it was worth it.
我們找到一個手機號碼
We got a number.
克羅伊正在追蹤
Chloe's running it down.
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
找到地址了嗎？
Did you get an address?
是的
Yes.
我打開了這個區域的視頻監控系統
I opened the CCTV cameras in the area.
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
到處都是警察和醫務人員
There are police and paramedics everywhere.
有個女的被車撞了
A woman was hit by a bus.
我細看了一下
I just got a closer look at her.
制作人
金相圭
是西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲
It's Simone Al-Harazi.
她還活著嗎？
Is she alive?
應該是吧
I think so.
我不知道，看上去不太好
I don't know, it doesn't look good.
她剛被抬進了救護車
She's just been put into the ambulance.
看到瑪戈了嗎？
Any sign of Margot?
我沒看到
Not that I can see.
她被送去哪家醫院？
Which hospital are they taking her to?
赶紧离开
联合执行制片人
托尼·巴士加仑普
克羅伊，是哪家醫院？
Chloe, Chloe which hospital?
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
離那兒最近的是聖愛德華醫院
St. Edward's, it's the closest in the area.
傑克，我得走了
Jack, I got to go.
克羅伊
Chloe.
监 制
基弗·萨瑟兰
怎麼了？
What happened?
西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲被車撞了
Simone Al-Harazi just got hit by a bus.
被送去了聖愛德華醫院
They're taking her to St. Edward's Hospital.
监 制
强·卡萨
大卫·弗瑞
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
曼尼·科托
监 制
伊万·卡茨
這是20分鐘前秘密交給我們的
It was back-channeled to us about 20 minutes ago.
我們的技術人員花了好一會兒
Took our communications guys a little while
才弄明白
to figure out what it was.
监 制
霍华德·高登
你確定這是瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的
Are you sure that this is contact information
聯絡資料？
for Margot Al-Harazi?
確定，閣下
Yes, sir.
她為什麼發這個？
Why would she send this?
這是她計劃的一部分，閣下
It's part of her game, sir.
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
要你認罪的最後期限就快到了
The deadline for you to surrender yourself is approaching.
她這是要激您和她談條件
She... is daring you to discuss terms.
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
我們能利用這個定位她嗎？
Can we use this to locate her?
我已經問過了，視頻數據流經過加密
I've already asked... it's a secured video data stream
编 剧
托尼·巴士加仑普
無法追蹤源地址
there's no way to trace it back to its source.
謝謝你，馬克
Thank you, Mark.
我接個電話
I have to take this.
通话安全
傑克
Jack.
總統閣下
Mr. President.
导 演
强·卡萨
你說的那人怎麼樣了？
What's happening with you guy
他交代阿爾哈拉茲的藏身之處了嗎？
did he give up Al-Harazi's location?
我們還在追蹤電話號碼
We're still running numbers
不過我們有她女兒西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲的線索
but we got a lead on her daughter, Simone Al-Harazi.
她在一場車禍中受傷了
She was injured in a traffic accident.
我們認為她媽媽還不知道這事
We don't think her mother knows about it yet
我們想隱瞞這件事
and we want to try and keep it that way.
救護車送她去聖愛德華醫院了
She's being transported in an ambulance to St. Edward's Hospital.
我會馬上派人看好她
I'll have her put under immediate guard.
謝謝，總統閣下
Thank you, sir.
我需要全權審問她
I'm gonna need full access to her.
我現在沒職權
I have no authority here
我不想與英國警方這樣周旋下去
and I don't want to keep working against British police.
您有什麼辦法嗎？
Is there anything you can do?
我會讓他們全力配合你的
You'll have complete cooperation.
總統閣下，還有一件事
Mr. President, there's one more thing.
軍情五處的特工妨礙了我們的行動
Our operation was interrupted by MI5 agents
很糟糕
it was a disaster.
他們說是受戴維斯首相之命前往的
They said they were ordered there by Prime Minister Davies.
怎麼會這樣？
How the hell did that happen?
很抱歉，傑克
I'm sorry about that, Jack.
我必須讓他相信我們
I had to take him into our confidence
以便說服他
in order to convince him
不在街上進行軍事部署
not to put soldiers on the street.
他向我保證過不會介入
He promised me he wouldn't interfere.
閣下，我們說好的可不是這樣
Sir, that wasn't the deal we made.
他們至少有5名特工犧牲
At least five of his men were killed.
總統閣下
Mr. President.
戴維斯首相來了
Prime Minister Davies is here to see you.
他來了，首相已經到了
He's here. The prime minister has arrived
不說了，傑克
I got to go, Jack.
詹姆斯，我想你已經聽說了發生的事情
James, I-I take it you've heard what's happened
我明確要求過你
I explicitly asked you
讓傑克·鮑爾
to allow Jack Bauer
獨自處理這件事！
to handle this alone!
你答應過我的
Now you gave me your word.
我只是答應推遲在街上進行軍事部署
I only agreed to hold off a military presence on the streets.
相信一個叛逃特工
Trusting a fallen agent
完全是另外一回事
is another matter entirely.
我們的監視發現他要背叛你
Our surveillance shows that he was betraying you
你們根本就不該監視他！
You had no business surveilling him in the first place!
我們距離瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的截止時間
We are approaching less than an hour
不到一個小時了
to Margot Al-Harazi's deadline.
你不把自己交給她
When you fail to deliver yourself to her
她打算把這個城市炸成廢墟
she plans to reduce this city to rubble and flames
我不能就這樣袖手旁觀
I can't just sit idly by and do nothing.
沒有人在袖手旁觀
Nobody is sitting idly by
大家都忙得焦頭爛額
we're working our asses off here.
我們要攜手合作！
You and I need to be working together!
我們攜手努力過了
We have worked together
而且認識彼此多年了，詹姆斯
and we have known each other for years, James.
我把你當朋友
I consider you a friend
正常情況下，我絕不會
and under normal circumstances I am not one
質疑你的判斷
who would ever doubt your judgment.
但是呢？
But?
但是
But
你是不是有什麼瞞著我，詹姆斯？
is there something you've been holding back from me, James?
比如說你的身體？
Concerning your health?
我身體怎麼了？
What about my health?
如果我聽說的是真的
If what I've heard is true
我深表同情
you have my deepest sympathy.
如果你擔心我的身體
If you had a concern regarding my health
應該直接過來問我
you should've come to me directly and asked.
我正問著呢
I'm asking you now.
若我的身體狀況
If I thought for one moment
會牽扯到他人一絲的安危
that my health risks anyone's life
我就馬上辭去總統一職
I would resign this presidency immediately.
我錯了，總統先生
My mistake, Mr. President.
敬請諒解
Please, accept my apologies.
我們還有機會
There's still a chance
來避免這次全面進攻
that we can avoid a full-scale attack.
且不說你的干涉
Despite your intervention
鮑爾能夠獲悉阿爾哈拉茲的情報
Bauer has a line on Al-Harazi.
這次我們還能信賴你的合作麼？
Now, can we count on your cooperation this time?
我親自向你保證
I personally give you my word
我們會提供他的一切所需
that he will have everything he needs.
謝謝
Thank you.
重度昏迷
We've got a GCS 3
無刺激反應
no response to stimuli.
血壓正常，140/60
BP's still good, 140/60.
顱內可能損傷
Head and probable internal injuries.
右側開放性骨折
Compound fracture to the right radius.
左手小指缺失
Missing finger on the left hand
與車禍無關
not related to the accident
像是最近造成的
looks like a recent injury.
喂？
Hello?
呃，你是哪位？
U- Uh, who-who is this?
我是倫敦急救中心人員
I'm with the London Ambulance Service.
這有一名創傷病人
We have a trauma patient
二十多歲，女性，紅褐色頭髮
a 20s female with reddish-brown hair.
您是她朋友還是親屬？
Are you a friend of hers or a relative?
她是我女兒
She's my daughter.
發生什麼了？
What, what-what's happened?
她被公交撞了
She was struck by a bus.
正被送往聖愛德華醫院急診室
We're taking her to the A&E Department at St. Edward's.
她不會有事吧？
I- Is she going to be all right?
我們會盡一切努力救治
We're doing everything that we can for her.
希望您能盡快
And you need to make your way to the hospital
趕往醫院
as soon as possible.
警方可能想跟您談談
The police are probably gonna want to talk to you.
好的，我…我馬上就過去
Of course. I... I'll be there straightaway.
能告知我您的姓名麼？
Could you tell me your name?
西蒙娜出了事故
Simone's been in an accident.
警方捲進來了
The police are involved.
警方？
The police?
他們認出她了麼？
Do they know who she is?
我不知道！
I don't know!
納維德的姐姐和孩子呢
What about Naveed's sister and child
她解決她們了沒有？
did she take care of them or not?
聖愛德華醫院附近
Who do we have in the area?
我們有誰在？
St. Edward's Hospital.
呃，卡裏姆
Uh, Kareem
他就住附近
he lives nearby.
派他去
Send him.
瞭解她的傷勢狀況
Have him find out how badly she's hurt
還有警方是否認出了她
and if they know who she is.
数据恢复程序运行中
哦
Oh.
加文
Gavin.
你在幹嘛？
What are you doing?
沒什麼
Oh, nothing.
什麼事？
What do you want?
埃裏克讓我把早先的
Erik wants me to pull up
監控文件調出來
the body cam files from earlier.
需要你的訪問密碼
I need your access code.
直接發你文件不就好了？
Why don't I just send you the files directly.
隨便你
Hey, suit yourself.
還有別的事麼？
Anything else?
沒了
No.
盡快發過來就行了
Just send over the files as quick as you can.
喂？
Yes?
你說過要停止分析員恢復
You said you were going to stop your analyst from retrieving
亞當·摩根被刪分區文件的
the deleted partitions from Adam Morgan's files.
是的
That's right.
我讓他沒管了
I ordered him to leave it alone.
恐怕你的話沒起作用
I'm afraid your order's not being followed.
他正在運行一項數據恢復程序
He's running a data retrieval program right now.
你們能夠訪問我們系統
You have access to our systems.
當然
Of course we do.
如果他看到了那些分區，就會知道
If he sees those partitions, he's going to know that
我賣給中國的情報來源於你
you're the source of intel I've been selling to China.
他們要不了多久就會發現是你陷害了亞當
How long before they reckon you framed Adam?
他只是個孩子
He's just a kid.
你寧願下半輩子都去蹲大牢？
You'd prefer prison for the rest of your life?
有人能派給我麼？
Is there someone you can send me?
清理工？
A cleaner?
聽著，我只是個中間人
Look, I'm just a middleman here.
你酬勞不菲
You've been well-paid.
盡快解決
Sort it out. Quickly.
你是負責人麼？
Are you in charge?
我是海倫·麥卡錫探長，你一定是鮑爾
Chief Inspector Helen McCarthy. You must be Bauer.
內政部讓我過來等你
The Home Office told me to expect you.
我會給予你一切協助
I'll give you any support you need.
多謝
Thank you.
這是摩根特工
This is Agent Morgan.
西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲在哪？
Where's Simone Al-Harazi?
她仍然不省人事
She's still unconscious.
醫生還在搶救
Doctor's working on her now.
發生什麼了？
What happened?
據目擊者稱
According to witnesses
她在追一個小女孩時被一輛公交撞倒
she was chasing after a young girl when the bus hit her.
那個女孩叫雅斯敏·阿齊贊
Girl's name is Yasmin Azizan.
她聲稱西蒙娜殺了她媽媽
She claims Simone murdered her mother.
兩名警員核實了地址
Two officers checked out the address
找到了她媽媽法拉·阿齊贊
found the mother, Farah Azizan
死於刺傷
dead from a stab wound.
這之間有什麼聯繫？
What's the connection?
她嚇壞了，沒說多少
Girl's not saying much. She's in shock.
她現在在哪？
Where is she right now?
在樓下急診室做檢查
Downstairs in A&E being checked over.
好的，我去跟她談談
Okay, I'm gonna go talk to her.
好
Okay.
這一塊全部戒嚴，只許指定人員進出
We need to clear this entire wing, authorized personnel only.
好的，馬上就辦
Okay, I'll get on to it.
醫生正等著跟您講話
The doctor's waiting to speak to you.
她情況怎麼樣了？
What's her condition?
還在觀察中
We're still looking.
我們試圖在CT掃瞄前讓她情況保持穩定
We're trying to get her stable before we do a CT scan.
她醒了麼？
Is she awake?
還沒
No.
但正在恢復知覺
But she's coming around.
好
Okay, good.
掃瞄之前
I'm gonna need to talk to her
我要跟她講上話
before you send her in for that scan.
這不可能
That's not possible.
醫生，我不是在問你行不行
Doctor, I'm not asking.
現在有更多人的性命比她還危急
Right now there are more lives at stake than just hers.
我需要你盡一切可能穩定她的情況
I need you to do what you can to stabilize her
讓她保持清醒，明白麼？
and get her conscious. Do you understand me?
求你了
Please.
好吧，注射四十毫克腎上腺素
Okay, 40 milligrams of adrenaline, please.
華盛頓護士，請撥4203
Nurse Washington, call 4203.
Nurse Washington, 4203.
是雅斯敏嗎？
Is this Yasmin?
我能和她坐一會兒麼？
Mind if I sit with her a while?
我沒事了
I'm all done here.
希望你喜歡薑汁汽水
Hope you like ginger beer.
我叫凱特
My name's Kate.
介意我問你幾個問題麼？
You mind if I ask you a couple questions?
你是美國人？
You're American?
嗯，是的
Mm-hmm, yeah. That's right.
你知道
You know
我知道這一切對你來說不容易
I know that this isn't easy for you and all
你媽媽的事，我很抱歉
and I'm really sorry about your mom.
你能跟我說說那個女人
Can you tell me about what happened
在場時的情形嗎？
about the woman who did this?
西蒙娜舅媽？
Aunt Simone?
她是你舅媽？
She's your aunt?
西蒙娜·阿爾哈拉茲…你跟她有關係？
Simone Al-Harazi... you're related to her?
沙巴茲
Shabazz.
她叫西蒙娜·沙巴茲
Her name's Simone Shabazz.
幾年前嫁給了我舅舅納維德
She married my uncle Naveed a couple of years ago.
當時我在房間裏寫作業
I was in my room doing my homework
聽到了叫聲
when I heard shouting.
她們在吵架？
They were arguing?
我聽到媽媽說
I heard my mum say
她要報警
that she was going to call the police.
她衝著我喊
She was shouting for me
叫我出去
telling me to get out.
當我下來時
When I came down
就看到
I saw
看到我媽媽，還有血
I saw my mum and the blood.
嘿，沒事了
Hey, it's okay.
你還記得西蒙娜舅媽說了什麼嗎？
Do you remember anything that your aunt Simone said?
她告訴媽媽說，我們得離開倫敦
She told Mum that we had to get out of London.
還說她在試圖保護我們
She said she was trying to protect us.
免受她媽媽的傷害
From her mother.
對，呃…瑪戈
Right, uh... Margot.
你認識她麼？
Do you know her?
知道她可能在哪裏麼？
Do you know where she might be?
我從沒見過她
I never met her.
我知道了，你是一個非常勇敢的女孩
Okay, well, you know what, you are a very brave girl.
非常謝謝你能跟我說這些
Thank you so much for talking to me.
我會找機會回來看你的，好麼？
I'm gonna try and come back and see you again, okay?
西蒙娜舅媽會怎麼樣？
What's going to happen to her... Aunt Simone?
我不知道
I don't know.
我希望她死掉
I hope she dies.
喂
Yeah.
你跟西蒙娜說上話了嗎？
Were you able to talk to Simone?
沒有，醫生還在對她進行救治
No, doctor's still working on her
設法讓她清醒過來
trying to get her conscious.
好
Right.
叫雅斯敏的那個女孩是西蒙娜的外甥女
This girl Yasmin is Simone's niece.
她不認識瑪戈，但是
She doesn't know Margot, but she
她說在意外發生之前
said that before the situation went south
西蒙娜力勸她們離開倫敦
Simone was urging them to get out of London.
她說西蒙娜在試圖保護她們
She said that she was trying to protect them
不受她媽媽的傷害
from her own mother.
你確定？
Are you sure?
是，那女孩是這麼說的
Yeah, according to the girl.
我是說，我聽起來
I mean, it sounds to me
像是西蒙娜在背叛她母親，也就是說
like Simone was betraying her own mother, which means we've
我們有很大機會能策反她
got a great chance at turning her.
我這就回去找你
I'm on my way back to you.
好
Okay.
她怎麼樣了？
How is she?
我目前還沒見到她
I haven't seen her yet.
我不知道她在哪裏
I don't know where she is.
進來倒是很容易，但是
It was easy getting in, but
警察已經開始封鎖這個地方了
the police are starting to lock the place down.
他們知道她的身份了
They know who she is.
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
他們會用一切手段
They're going to do everything
逼她開口
they can to get her talking.
我覺得她可能
I don't think she's
不用怎麼逼就會開口了
going to need much persuading.
什麼意思？
What does that mean?
那個女孩，呃，雅斯敏
The girl, um, Yasmin
她沒有殺她
she left her alive.
一個美國女人去詢問她
An American woman was questioning her.
她說西蒙娜
She said Simone was
提醒她們要離開倫敦
warning them to get out of London?
還說她在試圖保護她們不受你的傷害
Said she was trying to protect them from you.
找到她在那棟樓裏的確切位置
Find out exactly where she is in the building.
剩下的交給我們
We'll take care of the rest from here.
遵命
Will do.
讓大家開始收拾東西
Have everyone start packing up.
收拾東西，我們要走了
Start loading, we're leaving.
不必如此吧
You don't have to do this.
她已經背叛過我一次了
She's betrayed me once.
我不會再犯同樣的錯誤
I won't let her do it again.
伦 敦
調動無人機，把那所醫院置於打擊範圍之內
Move the drone to within range of the hospital.
我剛剛參加了
I've just attended
政府緊急事件委員會的會議
a meeting of the government's emergency committee.
會上我接到了
Where I received
有關部長和官員的完整報告
a full report from the appropriate ministers and officials.
相信你們大多數人已經瞭解到
As most of you are already aware
不久前我們收到通知
we received notice of an imminent
一次針對倫敦的恐怖威脅迫在眉睫
terrorist threat to London short while ago.
由於我們相信該威脅的真實性
Since we believe this threat's to be credible
我已經下令首都城市高度警戒
I've ordered that our capital city be put on critical alert.
作為預警，我
As a precaution, I'm
喬丹，可以到我這兒來一下嗎？
Jordan, can you step in here for a moment?
當然可以
Sure.
我重複一遍，這僅僅是
Again, this is simply
一個預警，七年來在這個國家裏
a precaution. We have not seen a successful
還沒有發生過一次成功的襲擊
attack on this country in seven years.
但是沒有發生襲擊
But the absence of an attack
沒出什麼事吧？
Everything okay?
卡姆登市有一個秘密傳遞情報點
There's a dead drop over in Camden.
我們的一個高級情報人員在那裏留下一個包裹
One of our high-level assets left a package
可能有找到瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的線索
with possible leads to Margot Al-Harazi.
我需要你去把它取回來
I need you to pick it up.
我？
Me?
你要派我去執外勤？
You're sending me into the field?
我們人手不夠了
We're shorthanded.
今天我們失去了很多特工
We lost a lot of agents today.
埃裏克身體狀況不佳去不了，所以
Erik's not fit enough to go out, so
我得靠你了
I'm relying on you.
要是你幹不了，就直說
If you're not up to it, just say the word.
不，不，我當然幹得了
No, no. Sure. I can do that.
這事機密性高，不要外傳
It's important this stays between us.
情報點在水閘處的一個遊艇上
The drop's at a houseboat on the lock.
找到包裹，把它帶回來
Make the pickup and bring the package back.
夠清楚了嗎？
Straightforward enough for you?
是的，好的
Yeah. Okay.
好
Good.
謝謝您的信任，長官
Thank you for trusting me with this, sir.
你應得的
You've earned it.
在危機結束之前，所有士兵都受命
Soldiers have been instructed to help keep order
幫助維護秩序
until the crisis passes.
警戒期間
Emergency services
所有應急服務將持續處於運營狀態
will remain operational throughout the alert.
地鐵交通系統，鐵路運輸系統
The underground, rail
和公交系統
and bus services
你還好嗎？
You all right?
嗯，我沒事
Yeah, I'm fine.
戴維斯終於把恐怖威脅公之於眾了
Davies is finally going public on the terror threat.
我知道，之前我跟首相交談過
I know. I had a conversation with the prime minister earlier.
他知道我的身體狀況了，他向我問起這事
He knows about my condition. He asked me about it.
您怎麼說？
What did you say?
我處理得不是很好
I didn't handle it very well.
但是也沒什麼，用不了多久
But it doesn't matter. It won't be long
其他人也都會發現的，我做的每一件事
before others find out. Everything I do
我下的每一個決定，都會受到批判
every decision I make will be second-guessed.
我的管理已經不可能再維持下去了
It will be impossible for me to govern.
爸爸，你說過你只想要完成你的任期
Dad, you said that you wanted to just finish out your term.
我這麼想真是
It was arrogant, vain
自負，徒勞又愚蠢
and stupid of me to even think that.
馬克
Mark
等危機結束我們回到華盛頓
when the crisis is over and we get back to Washington
你安排下跟副總統開個會
I want you to set up a meeting with the vice president
我們讓他為交接做好準備，明白嗎？
so we can bring him up to speed on the transition, yeah?
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
你能聽到我說話嗎？
Can you hear me?
西蒙娜，你能聽到我說話嗎？
Simone, can you hear me?
我在哪裏？
Where am I?
你遇到了車禍，現在你要聽我說
You've been in an accident. Right now I need you  to listen to me.
雅斯敏
Yasmin.
她很好，她很安全
She's fine. She's safe.
她跟我們說你試圖讓她和她媽媽
She told us that you tried to get her and her mother
離開倫敦，你試圖保護她們
to leave London. You tried to protect them.
你還記得嗎？
Do you remember that?
我認識你
I know you.
你是在地鐵裏跟著我的那個人
You were following me on the underground.
我叫傑克·鮑爾
My name is Jack Bauer.
西蒙娜，你的本性讓你保護自己的家人
Simone, your instinct was to protect your family members
不受你母親今日所作所為的傷害
from what your mother is doing today.
我希望你能考慮一下，如果
I want you to think of the hundreds of thousands
我們不制止她，將會有多少無辜的人被害
of innocent people that will die if we don't stop her.
求你幫助我
Please help me.
現在只有你能
Right now you're the only person
阻止這件事情的發生
that can stop this from happening.
就因為我可憐法拉和雅斯敏
Just because I took pity on Farah and Yasmin
不等於說我就會向你出賣我母親
doesn't mean I would ever betray my mother to you.
你母親
Your mother
是誰幹的？
who did this?
我母親她很愛我
My mother loves me.
她絕對不會
She would never do anything
傷害我的
to harm me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不該那麼做的
I shouldn't have done that.
我只是很討厭這些人
I just hate these people.
他們總以為有什麼事情
For thinking there could be anything
能為他們的罪行辯護
that would justify what they're doing.
她反正也不會說的
She wasn't gonna talk anyway.
那個小女孩
The young girl
那個外甥女，雅斯敏
the niece, Yasmin.
你覺得她能策反她嗎？
Do you think she can turn her?
傑克，她心靈受到創傷
Jack, she's traumatized.
她親眼看著自己的媽媽死在西蒙娜的手裏
She watched her mother die by Simone's hand.
她很怕她
She's terrified of her.
我們沒有時間了
We're running out of time.
瑪戈設的期限就要到了
Margot's deadline's almost up.
嘿，我們不是封鎖了整個樓層麼
Hey. I thought we locked down this entire floor.
無關人員免進的，他是誰？
Authorized personnel only. Who's he?
我們封鎖了
We did.
不好意思，請給我看下你的證件
Excuse me, I need to see your ID.
抱歉，我
sorry. I
我可能上錯樓層了
I think I'm on the wrong floor.
不好，趴下！
It's not right. Get down!
你還好嗎？
You all right?
嗯
Yeah.
走電梯
Take the elevator.
堵住出口
Cover the exit.
好
Okay.
靠
Damn it.
你左邊
You take the left.
動手
Now.
安全，安全
Clear. Clear.
我看到他了
I got him.
你！站住！
You! Stop!
趴下！
Stay down!
讓開！讓開！
Move! Move!
站那兒別動！
Stop right there!
別開槍！
Don't shoot!
我靠！
Damn it!
他死了
He's dead.
他到底是誰？
Who the hell is he?
放下槍，放下槍
Stand down. Stand down.
一定是瑪戈派他來的
Margot must've sent him.
他給她發了西蒙娜的位置
He texted her Simone's location.
她在4楼东面病房
我有多少时间逃出去？
8分钟
她回復說…你有八分鐘時間離開那裏
She replied... you got eight minutes to get out.
那是什麼意思？
Well, what does that mean?
她要派一架無人機來殺掉她女兒
She's sending a drone to kill her daughter.
你得馬上疏散醫院裏的人
You need to clear this hospital now.
馬上！
Now!
讓大家都出去！
Get everyone out!
快！
Move!
我們得帶上西蒙娜
We got to get Simone.
你去吧，我在外面跟你會合
Keep going. I'll meet you outside.
一分鐘後鎖定目標
One minute to target.
克羅伊，我們能從我剛給你的號碼裏
Chloe, were we able to pull anything off the number
找到什麼線索嗎？
I just gave you?
不行，那是個改道的連接
Negative. It was a re-routed connection.
行不通，傑克
It's a dead end, Jack.
靠
Damn it.
醫生，把她交給我，你可以走了
Doctor, I've got her. You can go.
她沒法走路
She can't walk.
那也得走，快！
She's gonna have to. Go!
怎…怎麼了？
Wh-Wh... What's happening?
你媽正用無人機對準你
Your mother's targeting you with a drone.
不可能
No.
為了讓你閉嘴，她願意把這裏的人都殺了
She's willing to kill everybody here just to keep you quiet.
她不會這麼做的
She wouldn't do that.
你真這麼覺得？
You honestly believe that?
那你呆這兒吧
Stay here then.
等等
Wait.
請別扔下我
Please. Please don't leave me here.
我們得走了
We got to go now.
起來
Get up.
雅斯敏，那個女孩…有沒有看見她走？
Uh, Yasmin, the girl... did you see her leave?
沒注意
I didn't notice.
雅斯敏！
Yasmin!
雅斯敏，親愛的，是我，凱特
Yasmin, hey, sweetie, it's Kate.
我們得離開這裏，聽我說，我知道你很害怕
We got to get out of here. Listen, I know you're scared.
但我會照顧好你，好嗎？
But I'm gonna take care of you, okay?
來，我們得離開這裏
Come on. We got to get out of here. Come on.
醫院進入射程
Hospital in range.
快走，快！
Come on! Let's go! Come on!
進入定位程序
Starting the targeting sequence.
地狱导弹就绪
放大
Zoom in.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余4枚导弹
他們在撤離了
They're evacuating.
也許已經把西蒙娜救出來了
They may have gotten Simone out already.
還是要發射
Fire anyway.
傑克！跟我走！
Jack! Follow me!
地狱导弹就绪
剩余4枚导弹
目標鎖定
Target acquired.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余3枚导弹
沒事了，親愛的
It's all right, sweetheart.
沒事了
You're gonna be all right.
探長，把這個女孩兒帶走
Chief Inspector, take the girl.
等西蒙娜安全了，我馬上聯繫你
As soon as Simone is secure, I'll contact you.
沒事了！
It's gonna be okay!
掃瞄這片區域，找到她
Scan the area. If they got her out, find her.
看到了
I got her.
在那裏
There they are.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余3枚导弹
鎖定目標
Lock on target.
然後發射
And fire.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余3枚导弹
目標鎖定
Target acquired.
她應該看見我們了，坐好
She's got a visual on us. Hold on.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余2枚导弹
跟住
Stay on them.
一有機會就發射
Take the shot when you can.
西蒙娜，她不幹掉你是不會停手的
Simone, she's not gonna stop until she kills you.
我們必須制止她，只有你能幫我們
We've got to stop her. You're the only one who can help us.
而你只需要告訴我們你母親在哪裏就可以了
All you need to do is tell us where your mother is.
傑克！
Jack!
嘗試鎖定目標
Trying to acquire target.
抓住了
Got them.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余2枚导弹
發射
Firing.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余1枚导弹
我擦！
Damn it!
我得把飛機下降到兩萬英尺
I need to bring it down to 20,000 feet.
這樣他就不可能逃脫了
He won't be able to evade it then.
行，要多久？
Okay, but how much time?
我們只剩最後一枚導彈了
We're down to our last missile.
其他無人機不在射程內
The other drones aren't in range yet. If we miss
要是失手就沒機會了
we don't have another chance.
擦！等等
Damn it! Hold on.
我們得換車了，跟我來
We're gonna switch cars. Follow my play.
媽的
Damn it.
嘿，老兄
Hey, buddy.
你沒事的
You're all right.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余1枚导弹
正在鎖定新的目標車輛
Acquiring the new target vehicle.
媽的，沒法鎖定
Bloody hell. I couldn't get a lock.
傑克
Jack.
看到了
I see it.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余1枚导弹
還得換車
We got to switch cars.
拿上我的包
Grab my bag.
在這兒等著
Wait here.
下車！快！
Get out of the car! Now!
下車！動作點！
Get out! Move!
走
Go.
你們CIA分局裏有醫務室嗎？
Is there an infirmary at your CIA station?
有
Yes.
好，那就去那裏，等等
Okay, that's where we're going. Hold on.
你…別動
You... don't you move.
地狱导弹就绪
剩余1枚导弹
鎖定了
I've got them.
目标已摧毁
剩余0枚导弹
贊！
Yes!
回放
Take it back.
目标已摧毁
剩余0枚导弹
車裏沒人！
It's empty!
目标已摧毁
剩余0枚导弹
傑克，她情況很差
Jack, she's in bad shape.
副部長，多謝您抽時間見我
Deputy Minister, thank you for taking the time to see me.
倫敦已經開始宵禁，我們不應該出來的
London is under curfew. We shouldn't be out here.
那我長話短說，布德羅先生
So I shall make this brief, Mr. Boudreau.
我堅持要求你把犯人傑克·鮑爾交給我
I insist that you hand over the criminal Jack Bauer.
這個，情況有變
Well, circumstances have changed.
鑒於目前的反恐形勢
President Heller has enlisted Bauer's help
海勒總統已經徵召鮑爾協助政府
in the current terrorist situation.
可以說，引渡令簽得有點太草率了
The rendition order was signed in haste, shall we say.
我想那應該不是海勒總統簽的吧
But not by President Heller, I think.
您什麼意思？
Excuse me?
所以你一直不願意讓他跟莫斯科通話
That's why you're so reticent to put him on the phone to Moscow.
他根本不知道這事
He doesn't know about this.
我們知道你夫人跟鮑爾的舊情
We know about your wife's history with Bauer.
所以我理解你為何對情敵這麼做
I understand why a man like you would take actions against a rival.
別把我太太扯進來
Leave my wife out of this.
但如果我沒說錯的話
But if I'm not mistaken, forging a president's
偽造總統簽名
signature would be considered
可是叛國罪
an act of treason.
一旦被發現，你覺得你的事業，你的婚姻
What do you think will happen to your career
會是怎樣一種結局？
to your marriage, if you were found out?
聽著…你這麼恐嚇我
Look, it's, uh... it's pointless
是毫無意義的
to try to intimidate me.
鮑爾現在是拿著總統令在外勤
Bauer is out on the field on presidential order.
就算我想，我也碰不了他
I couldn't get my hands on him if I wanted to.
那你什麼意思？
So what are you saying now?
我好朋友米哈伊爾·諾亞科維奇被殺
That the man responsible
我們的總統被人試圖暗殺
for murdering my good friend Mikhail Novakovich
而應該為此負責的那個人
and attempting to assassinate our president
卻沒法讓我們繩之以法？
will not be turned over to us to face justice?
我的意思是
I'm saying
給我時間
give me time.
一旦鮑爾完成他的任務
Once Bauer serves his purpose
大家就都能得到自己想要的了
everyone gets what they want.
我們缺的正是時間
Time we do not have.
為你自己著想，最好快點
Make it sooner than later, for your sake.
我等你電話
I expect your call.
圣爱德华医院发生爆炸
恐怖分子发射导弹袭击伦敦医院
她怎樣？
How is she?
脈搏微弱
Her pulse is weak.
請講
Go ahead.
傑克
Jack
我在看醫院發生的事件
I'm watching the devastation at the hospital.
太殘忍了
Brutal.
是的，閣下，我們想辦法把西蒙娜弄了出來
Yes, sir. We managed to get Simone out.
但她情況很差
She's in bad shape.
我們正把她往CIA分局帶
We're taking her over to the CIA station.
那裏有醫務室
They have an infirmary.
我們得想辦法讓她活下去
We're gonna try and keep her alive.
你跟她說話了嗎？
Did you talk to her?
她有說瑪戈在哪裏嗎？
Did she tell you where Margot is?
沒有，長官，還沒說
No, sir, not yet.
你覺得有希望
Any realistic chance
在時限之內找到瑪戈嗎？
that we'll find Margot before the deadline?
總統先生，我們還在努力
Mr. President, we're still trying.
但說實話，時間不多了
And to be honest with you, we're running out of time.
我要見你，傑克
I'm going to have to see you, Jack.
閣下？
Sir?
等你到這裏
I'll explain it to you
我會跟你解釋
when you get here.
遵命，閣下
Yes, sir.
總統要見我
The president needs to see me.
那她呢？
And what about her?
官邸順路
Residence is on the way.
我先下，你帶她去醫務室
You can drop me off, and then take her over to the infirmary.
進來
Come in.
圣爱德华医院发生爆炸
恐怖分子发射导弹袭击伦敦医院
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲的聯繫方式…按您的要求
Contact information on Margot Al-Harazi... back-channeled
我們用非官方渠道拿到的
per your request, sir.
外套放椅子上
Put the jacket on the chair.
不要跟任何人提起這事，包括布德羅
Not a word about this to anyone, including Boudreau.
明白嗎？
Do you understand?
當然
Of course.
我們這是要？
What exactly are we, uh?
謝謝
Thank you.
瑪戈·阿爾哈拉茲
Margot Al-Harazi.
海勒總統
President Heller.
我很驚訝
I'm surprised.
我以為你沒膽給我打電話
I didn't think you were man enough to make this call.
你給了我時限
You gave me a deadline
要求我向你投降
and asked me to surrender myself to you.
如果願意的話，我還是有時間選擇同意的
I still have time to comply if I choose.
既然來了電話
The fact you've made contact suggests to me
說明你已經決定了
you've already reached your decision.
如果我按你的要求向你投降
If I do as you ask and surrender myself to you
我是否可以相信你說的那些話？
can I trust you to keep your word?
你問是否可以相信我？
You're asking if you can trust me?
我覺得咱倆之中有疑慮的那個應該是我才對吧
If either of us should be suspicious, it's me.
你是在耍詐給自己爭取時間嗎？
Is this a tactic to buy yourself more time?
不是
No tactic.
沒人知道我們在通話
No one else knows about this.
只有你和我
It's just you and me
一對一
reaching out to one another.
這樣的話…那麼是的
If that's true... then, yes.
按照之前的要求向我投降
Surrender yourself to me on the terms I set out
那我保證這事就算完了
and you have my word this will be over.
不會再死一個人
Nobody else will die.
我在等你的決定
I'm waiting for your decision.
如你所言
As you suggested
我已經有了決定
my decision has already been made.
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs